Are the sales increasing or not,
it is continuously increasing from jail, from
10 most important is mouse a margin,
Yasmin, the margins
of very love you
a right ten in the profit is 34, boil that what
you are saying is also correct, you have done
doctor,
so in cost 80%, 70% material I am
taking class,
information will remain at some time, so that
time can be that margin categories, right
Malik, tonight I must have
written on it above, is there any,
Ajay, let's
take it to the top, it is
written in this note that
in the correction incomplete deck, you had vacant
years available, I brought it from Pakistan
from the annual report, sir and that app is needed, that is
and I am a different question, I have
kept in two, if there is any other company in this sector,
you can pay attention here too, isn't it
tasty back in my opinion, then you should check
that this is needed because
in the coming time, whatever you will get and that is,
children will get a lot  If you like all this, you want to have
breakfast, then we
can check which company is good and is it
consistent, that Pratap Sainik is consistent,
the receiver is comfortable, then you can move ahead also,
then Pratap is not in this company, there is a
lot of problem in India, that is why I
could not do it, there is a
recession going on and Pratap Select's
business is growing by 25 percent, the profit is
good, the profit is
100 percent, the profit
demand is tremendous, so this demand is in the
industry, now the company of the industry has to
take another company, there will be demand for them, which is good, they can give another
new result
in a new format, they do not give one and a half inch each, they
can do it separately, so
why not write in the comment, the subject is
still new in the industry, they did not get it, so
what did I do, their husband,
we did it quarter by quarter, that is why you did
not get it even in the report because it
is not a company at all and
A Professor Vijay Bhai Chandu, it is good
that we move forward, it acts as it
expects work  You have done it,
Vijay Bhai, okay, but let me tell you something, Roshni Vijay,
wonderful company,
system metal, has the highest margin among all the
new companies and
gives good dividends, okay, eat and a
few words, the
dorsal horn is even more consistent, it is consistent, it has never been like this in the
last so many
years, isn't it, and
what is this,
this SSC on JPU is a little down this time,
and something like this has come in it, and
Mutual Funds have also posted it, we will
put it down, you can see what
I have opened, reduce it a little,
this is SSC Jhala SST,
oh what is this data, enter the
latest SSC, subscribe to the motor, it is
very much, but it does
not make money in this world company immediately,
after that, it took a few lakhs and built its reader's
holding, on the 18th,
they did some DHA,
this BF has come, they also,
sorry Mirae Asset Mutual Fund, they also
bought some 5 like shares, so all these
companies are slowly increasing their holding
in it, why are they increasing it  Did
you guys even know anything about the
contestants here? You mentioned Martin, it's a
good business. Sister, most of them would be
energy exchanges, like the Positive
Energy Exchange and the National Stock Exchange. You can
buy these companies through them and they
do it, and they get better price
discovery from them. This system has been
running in developed countries for years. It was
launched in India some time ago. The
government and several institutions
started it together, that's why the dividend is also
good. This is a slow dentist who will
give good dividends
because this company is okay. There is no introduction,
like a BSc or MSc. There are no expenses for them. Their
margins were also good. Do
we need tight permission?
This is everyday. So yes, we
can definitely pay attention to this company. Vijay Bhai, you have
discovered the company very well and everything is good. You have done a
good job. The
investor presentation is a little good on the Patna PAC
side, and information about many things can be found.
Yes, sir, where can you find investors? Of course, okay, okay, okay, so we have
controlled it.
Now you have to control the result and write the presentation
on which you are working. Now when you write, if you
want information about the presentation made for these people, then
make a presentation for these people. These
people are also running such a business.
If there is a challenge in the coming time, then
this is positivity. If this is positive,
grh grh,
Vijay Bhai, since the time of IPO, I have also
commented on this. Now you will know
that because I have commented, hello, hello, I
should have said something like this,
sir, take this fifth, in 2018 its
face value was just one and a half inch, so one
word,
this plate will come, due to
this, can someone
price it? Please, about the tree,
yes, yes, anyone who distributes 50%
in liquid, then this can be the person
who can immediately know what
they can do, they can take more dividend
distribution company, they are of the
company which subscribes the channel,
what happens is that their villages do
not study much because they have enough money, let's
get the money tomorrow.  Money does not mean getting money,
because of the company's lack of expenses, people are computer
Ajay,
yours, so let's
go, thank you Vijay ji, okay, thank you
Salumbar Vikas ji, you have done a
good job, at first glance, it is a
company like this, a little bit of
disturbance from the Bigg Boss background, if the college is completely clear then ok,
listen to your voice, please tell me,
I am just coming from home to your sir, this is such an I number
company, this is basically the setup and this
company in 2018 again the previous song, the
speed of two consecutive two, which is approximately and we see its
long-term 60% special thing is growing at the same speed
and before this the sales of Rule 10 1 have increased,
they are there but I would like to mark 6 inches, they just
leave the office, which is not your fault,
this should have happened, if this had not happened then
I would have thought why the mistake was not made, now
how could something be reduced, for example, if you are researching a life
insurance company or
you are researching a general insurance company,
both these companies
What happens is that some other companies, now the
industry also comes under such companies, these
companies do half an hour and
charge a premium, if there is any increase
then their revenue increases, they get money,
we have to pay money, the rest of the time
everything goes well, some people have intentions, so
in life insurance also, life
insurance companies get money, there is
something in general insurance, people live in
these general insurance companies, these
companies have a huge cash reserve,
they keep getting good money,
so these companies keep saving the cash that comes to them, in
liquid funds, in debt funds, in many different
Amarchand funds, the government
invests more in different places,
what happens due to their investment, these companies invest so that
if any sudden event happens in the future, then
they should also have money at that time, if it is
divided into all the divisions then it will not work, then the
company
stands on your investments, the investments of every general and life insurance
company are big,
their income is every year, now pay a little
carefully, full naat rate Vikas ji, their income is of
two types, first income  The premium
skin has reduced, the second one is theirs, the
second one will be of typing,
they get interest every year on the investment they have made, so the interest income of your
companies increases on these premium incomes,
such a time comes,
you will search in central, in this entire thing
that you have taken and only the premium is
less
or their skin is not less, then what will you have to do, it is
well in the data, this is a
matter of fact, but you, okay, you have taken it for 2 years,
actually it is not that you have started paying thousand
crores, but what is this, which you have
taken from your side, in this there is insurance sorry in the
and their running in serious,
interest has not been taken,
any chip of the premium of two zale,
according to me you should take the total income, it is
increasing by 20% from last now, you searched well, okay,
good, as sir, you also told that if their
main expenditure is clean, then Bigg
Boss has about 50 pages, thank you
and the rest of it will almost come out
and a little different beneficiaries on the sample portion,  The
question is that it is
clamped on it,
if it had happened in the whole of India
that people had suffered losses, all those issues are in
their path that we will
get it to remove it, then 10
is less than [music] at this time, but still on average, the
behavior of tooth on development, the sales profit of looters
and GPS was removed in its range,
72 and 80 soil, answer stop last month,
more than mask, anyone by dividing it, that the
responsibility of the Eastern Western Railway Quarter Product which has been removed, Samsons Pet 6 Special is
not one that I tried to customize, you
please check, as you can see that
I have tried to customize, for that I have this,
I believe that
according to my space station, so
one thing that I tried to do is
support APS, I Ashish Beria to
remove 24, I
took it on base and the sorrow is that I am taking my date,
according to adulteration animals, so
like and you 296
in office Anu0 Emergent A  Like, I
broke the hold, so I
took the base of its 100th wicket zero khatti area 2025,
submitting it with these questions, I have
tried to extract it in its range,
share it, 60 to 80, all this is a
restaurant, but this plant for now or
check it once, this
is a general insurance company and there is no one else, even if there is no such thing, the
Jhumar will be looted for a good company, if
its pizza bread can
reach like 2030, then right now it is good,
its 740 stunt and now I have this
negative because if you grow like 200,
but on which we can do our extra, we will do this, due to which we
see fluctuations,
you have also come in Fortune 500, past
experience 1506, in that a Chinese company became, then
which general insurance company in India
can also become so big, which
company can come for free, then you
have the answer, just melt it, you try to do it, it happened
in 1968, increase this your  There has to be
some difference between the holding of a person and promoter,
promoter holding ceiling and
as far as the retailer is concerned, retailer's
holdings are also 0657. Now if we
try to find out what happened in the milk, then this
company is soon going to be an affair question. In this,
in two years,
Lootera Favorite Browser has f-18
hotspot holding, after the entire face, now only
Jyoti has sold its both legs by continuously selling
that if they were in the company before listing, then
these people were invested in the company for years
and the company kept moving ahead in Dwivedi.
These people had invested in the company many times, they bring
their experience
from other countries, backward insurance has to be
increased in India, we also have
experience, now we will invest money also,
their target is that in the coming 5, 6, 10
years, we will list the company, there will be
good elements, then we will
withdraw our money from this company and will invest in some other place,
this has also gone out of memory
and they must have made this investment after seeing some other opportunity,
so good thing and you will get to learn many things in this for
years  Sir, I had given you 19 minutes ago
Aadhar link welcome, I have
put my afternoon link in it, if I started at the time, it is
not a big deal
that you have done some work on HDFC Life, it has happened that
flight insurance has come on Bigg Boss,
I am a general insurance, York Life
Insurance has come, yes ok, I have done some work, that
you are
definitely talking, very good son, yesterday we
saw that video, relax, you have done a very good work,
these people feel that no,
just let me in today's session, okay, so let's go
here, you had
called, these people
also have a lot of income in general insurance, okay relax, I have done
f4 early in the morning, okay, open it, let
me check, yes Preeti madam, are you
online,
hello hello, yes madam, yes madam, welcome, good
morning, okay, I will make you a service
so that you can open this thing
in your laptop only because right now I
am here, so I will make you a service
madam so that you can explain it to us from your laptop
because it happens that Vikas bhai was
explaining something else and I  If someone else
was at the table then the mail gets a little mismanaged, so
if you explain it to me then you will know
where you are, so just give me a minute
Chintan Mehak Hardam I will make you Premshankar
so that he can present the network one
second,
what is your account name, that
it is on Preeti,
that you had to turn on
this dispute presenter now you can cut
madam mic mic mic mic is camera and
after camera it is written screen,
now by clicking on the screen you will be
able to activate it from your laptop, it
is visible in me, now if you take it down
you will find mic's disappointed
cream,
below it comment it is
primitive man, take it and take it to the place, in this
entire screen you will
see the mic, from here you will be able to unmute and
mute yourself, so first there is mic, then camera is
written and cost screen is written,
okay, it happened to you,
which screen is in front of you right now
madam, the same word is written in the laptop, madam
please share it easily,
800 OLX can be seen
As it is one of the demanding industries
which is calcium intelligent technology
company Wipro consumer intelligence
platform deliver consumer position
engagement
Ajay had
right to that
tensile channel mobile advertising
Meghnad means this is the same I mean
you are quite fond of it and liked it
and right now it is accused 814 half a
minute so you must be having problem
in finding the data how to find your
data oh
I had released this Saturday report and RSP so what did you
get to Chand madam will
give me
1000 rupees for its pen profit etc.
its sale is just one category so okay by the way
madam ji
torch light ford companies got listed so if
you see this data you must have
seen it finally mutual fund people will
also have questions so after the IPO did
any big mutual fund invest in
it after it came immediately got in SST that do
n't look at it like this so come here
this is Reliance Capital
I am good
and there is a company called Malwa India Fund Limited
and
That your Madam Vishesh of Malabar India
is a big investor who would have invested
before the IPO. Malabar has been investing
in this company for 4-1 years and now look,
even after the IPO, they have
increased their holding further. Now
this city has fallen a lot.
When the market fell,
then Malabar and Reliance would have suffered losses.
What would have happened, these people would have been
looted, loss to the family. Keeping this in mind,
Reliance Capital Shift note means
their hotel holding is 5.04 and I am on 19th.
Oh Madam, what happens to us, we buy a
wounded lion and then there is that hour,
I don't like it. There is no mutual fund in the guise of a crazy girl.
Avni was also taken and is still
living after that, so they will see this as an opportunity.
What will these people do in the fall and they will
add more and what do we think that
cumin means I have made some mistake.
I have also sent me good shares, so
these big investors just think a little
and we will have to do such a thing that no one has come who has fallen.
What is the condition of Rafi this
year,
son, did you see this year, their business is that it is a
big
loot,
this front currency, but their health is
good, sales have started from how many six questions
and the profit is showing hundred percent,
but still due to corona,
I have just got a problem of thirty percent, according to my
liking, I have to
calculate the final price of this current affair
and that is actually their business is
hundred percent, but you have
estimated 50% by taking likes or good day
loot madam corner, according to me,
should not the digital company have better technology, so people can do everything
online sitting at home or at different places, so there should
not be any problem,
but where could the problem be that the
companies which are taking advantage will also have
budget, so it is possible that the
advertising itself has come down, like
I read somewhere that Google has also
thought of reducing its cost of marketing,
with this, if this continues, people will reduce marketing
In this market, there can be some traps as well, we are
leaving side minutes,
show more
I am good, you did a great job
madam, wonderful work, ask and you got cigarettes from China
madam, anything else you would like to share with people,
I would like a fast company, anyway, Man
Singh is an industry, so I think
if we start this like we have 2050 and 2010
with you, then we can get
something good in it, son, we can expect a good group,
this computer can become good anyway,
when I am not good,
I have said that the distribution is
soon for 6 months because now it is listed, there will be
no option after listing
here, whereas if you have a six-month period, then
we get to know whether it is growing or
going down, so
what do you think from the admit card, how will the future be,
today's business can grow, it can grow,
exactly like the market,
in this case, maximize the entire industry well
etc., how to
type emotional, okay knowledge,
thank you, thank you, you want, then I  I am
telling you because you have done that improvement and
implementation is also very
difficult, why can't you do it and
you are able to do good to people in a very good way
because I feel that it is
not happening or not happening in yours,
I know
that Anushka Sharma used to
take it mostly according to share market and speculation, so it is
complete, I felt as if
someone else has taken a
pick, Deepak Bhai,
we have already discussed the demand once, but
Deepak ice is online right now,
thousands and
New Delhi Multi Color Time Indergarh, my
chemist shop's faith, put it in the level of selling medicines, that I have
come